porndig.com 2019-06-15

# Porndig Privacy Policy

Last update: 14/06/2018

#### 1\. Introduction

This document which complements our Terms and Conditions is intended to define the Porndig.com Website Privacy Policy and to inform you about how Porndig.com uses, processes and protects the information you transmit to us and that we collect.

This document may be modified at any time by Porndig.com in order to comply with any regulatory, legislative, jurisprudential or technological change.

Any such changes will be posted on this page and it is understood that by continuing to use the Porndig.com site you accept the amended Privacy Policy. You are therefore invited to consult this document regularly, for the latest update.

#### 2\. Personal data collected

Once you choose to become a user of this site, information is collected.

#### 2.1 Information that you transmit to us with your consent:

  * Your site login and password
  * Your email address
  * Your name
  * Your postal address
  * Your gender
  * Your sexual orientation
  * Your age
  * Your country
  * Your city

Note that some of this information is optional.

#### 2.2 Information we collect: 

  * Your IP address
  * The type of device used
  * Your operating system
  * Your web browser and its possible plugins
  * The country of origin of your connection
  * The pages of the Porndig.com site that you consult

#### 3\. Use of your personal data

The personal data we collect from you is generally used to provide you with relevant and personalised content, to improve customer service, to be able to contact you, for statistical purposes and more specifically for:

  * Allow you to access your account in case you lose your password
  * Allow you to receive gifts from the shop
  * Allow you to fill in your profile
  * Allow you to access certain features of the Porndig.com site
  * Allow us to communicate with you by email if this one is informed

#### 4\. Sharing your personal information

None of your personal data is exchanged, given, sold, transferred or shared with third parties.

#### 5\. Storage of your personal data

The data collected on the Porndig.com website are subject to measures such as the use of encryption technology to secure them and protect them against loss, modification, disclosure, access or unauthorized use.

Your personal data is hosted on our servers located in various datacenters which are subject to physical and technological protection such as the continuous presence of technicians and security agents, video surveillance, alarms, firewalls.

Access to your personal data is restricted solely to our employees who must access it in order to process it. These persons are subject by contract to confidentiality obligations.

#### 6\. About cookies

#### 6.1 What is a cookie?

A cookie is a small text file sent by a website to your browser and stored on your device, whether a computer, tablet, Smartphone or other device used on the website.

Cookies help to remember some of your settings and preferences, are used for statistical purposes and generally improve your user experience.

There are two types of cookies:

  * Session cookies that expire and disappear when you close your browser
  * Persistent cookies which have a fixed lifetime and disappear on a date defined by the site

The information collected and stored in cookies does not in any way identify you personally and does not contain any personal data that you entrust to us.

#### 6.2 How do we use cookies?

The Porndig.com website uses cookies for the following reasons:

  * Customize your user experience
  * Allow you to automatically login to your account
  * Provide you with personalized content
  * Perform statistics on the content of the site
  * Perform statistics on advertising links

#### 6.3 Do we use third-party cookies?

Yes Porndig.com uses third-party cookies provided by:

  * Yandex LLC through its Yandex Metrica service for statistical purposes under the following terms <https://yandex.com/legal/metrica_termsofuse>
  * Google Inc. through its Google Analytics service for statistical purposes under the following terms <https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245>
  * Cloudflare, Inc. through its hosting service to accelerate page loading and secure connections under the following terms <https://www.cloudflare.com/privacypolicy>
  * Pollux Network for statistical and advertising purposes in accordance with the following terms of its [Privacy Policy](https://www.polluxnetwork.com/assets/admin/docs/PRIVACY_POLICY_POLLUX_NETWORK_LLC.pdf "Privacy Policy") and its [Cookie Policy](https://www.polluxnetwork.com/assets/admin/docs/PLATFORM_COOKIE_POLICY_POLLUX_NETWORK_LLC.pdf "Cookie Policy")

#### 6.4 How to control your cookies?

Cookies are not essential to the operation of the site, but improve and facilitate your navigation. You can disable the use of cookies by changing the settings in your browser options or any other device used to access the Porndig.com site.

Note that such a modification may cause the site to malfunction or limit its functionality.

You can also visit [http://www.youronlinechoices.com](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/ "Youronlinechoices") to learn how to manage your cookies according to your browser and how to control and delete cookies related to advertising.

#### 7\. About notifications

Notifications are messages sent to your device used to access the Porndig.com website through your browser in order to occasionally send you information related to the Porndig.com website.

Where such notifications exist you must give us your consent for them to be enabled and displayed. You can, however, cancel the reception of notifications by going to your browser settings. Refer to your browser's help to find out how.

#### 8\. About the mailing

As part of our mailing campaigns we may send you emails in order to communicate information targeting your interests, to keep you informed of promotions, commercial offers and news about our products or services, or third-party products and services.

In the case of offers from third party partners your sensitive personal data is never transmitted.

These emails are always sent with your prior consent but you can unsubscribe at any time by clicking on the unsubscribe link in each email of this type.

#### 9\. Control your personal data

In accordance with European Union regulations, you may at any time request that your personal data be communicated, modified, updated, limited or deleted. Porndig.com undertakes to respond to any type of request within one month maximum from the date of receiving your request.

Please note that for legal or administrative reasons, we must keep some of your personal data for a maximum period of one year. In this case your personal data will be blocked in order to no longer be available for any use whatsoever.

Send your questions and requests about the protection of your personal data by sending a message via our contact page Porndig.com/contact

Because of our obligation of confidentiality and security of your personal data, we may ask you for documents proving your identity.

Porndig.com is also entitled to oppose any abusive or repetitive request.
